{
    "subject": "resource/John_C._McManus",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/description",
    "object": "military historian, writer, academic",
    "human_readable": "John C. McManus's description is that he is a military historian, writer, academic.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8154861927032471,
            "question": "Is John C. McManus involved in academic pursuits?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8112127780914307,
            "question": "What is John C. McManus's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.783538281917572,
            "question": "What could be some topics explored in John C. McManus's historical writings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7149080038070679,
            "question": "How does John C. McManus's background inform his historical perspectives?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6954041123390198,
            "question": "What are some areas of expertise for John C. McManus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6849537491798401,
            "question": "What is the nature of John C. McManus's writing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.54707932472229,
            "question": "Based on his description, what kind of audience might John C. McManus target?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46160250902175903,
            "question": "What are some potential institutions where John C. McManus might work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45852789282798767,
            "question": "How does John C. McManus contribute to the field of history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3550567626953125,
            "question": "What types of work might John C. McManus produce?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John C. McManus's description is that he is a military historian, writer, academic.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1922_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does John C. McManus contribute to the field of history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1922_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some potential institutions where John C. McManus might work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1922_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Based on his description, what kind of audience might John C. McManus target?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1922_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1922_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1922_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1922_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1922_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1922_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1922_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1922_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1922_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1922_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1922_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information and the query \"John C. McManus's description is that he is a military historian, writer, academic.\", here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention John C. McManus as an award-winning professor, author, and military historian in multiple instances (e.g., file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1922/re-ranker-msmarco/35.txt, 8.txt, 24.txt), which supports the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis response indicates that the information provided in the documents supports the statement that \"John C. McManus's description is that he is a military historian, writer, and academic.\" The documents repeatedly refer to John C. McManus as an author, professor, and military historian, thus validating this triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}